[Music]
[Applause]
Wow just look at the ocean you guys I
had no idea it was so [ __ ] big I know
what you mean Sonia it looks like it
goes on forever holy [ __ ]
make sure you kids put on lots of
sunscreen I don't want any of you
getting your asses burnt come on bro
wanna head over there and build a
sandcastle together Manik you know I
can't do that I'm not here to have fun
I'm here on a mission I can't keep being
a little [ __ ] boy forever it's time
that I finally learn how to swim are you
sure about this bro Sonia and I won't
think any less of you if you change your
mind yes my green bro I am sure it's
something I need to do not for me or for
you but for the man that I love
Bart levy I want to impress him and show
him I can do anything
you
I thought this would look on your cute
little ass don't open it until you're at
the bitch bitch love your boyfriend dart
lobby
[Music]
so uh Bart levy what do you think do you
think it makes me look cute Beach if I
wasn't sure you would look cute in it
do you really think I would have bought
it is is that so I hope you didn't spend
too much on me
don't worry [ __ ] that speed only cost
me thirty nine million dollars the pool
floaties were annexed to raped villain
each that is but pocket change to the
likes of me the ocean it looks so big so
big and scary like black people
mark levy I don't know if I can do this
don't worry [ __ ] just take it slow I
believe in you
maybe dip waters in to test the waters
of course if you don't want to that's
fine too
we can try again some other time the
Nami could head back over to the others
and build sandcastles or eat chili dogs
Thank You Bart levy but this is
something I need to do I can't just keep
being a little [ __ ] boy forever when it
comes to water I must face my demons I'm
sure I'll be okay if I just do my hose
in like you suggested what the hell was
that but you barely even touched it
I'm sorry Bartleby I just got so scared
I'll try again this time I'll try and
keep my feet and for about five seconds
you better coat I'm about 5 seconds away
from beating your [ __ ] ass are you
[ __ ] shooting me right now it's just
water you dumb [ __ ] I'm sorry Bart levy
I'll try again you're damn right you up
get in there [ __ ] I'm tired of you
being a [ __ ] [ __ ] when it comes to
water swimming
are you kidding me right now yo Sonia
your point [ __ ]
Eva Marie not intervenors in a special
request I'll say for the past six weeks
I'm sorry Uncle Chuck it was an accident
they just kind of fell off the tree
while I was scratching my butt cheeks
yet so don't yell at my sister old man
your hot dog smelled like Sonic [ __ ]
anyway
did I hear somebody talking about
wieners
I don't mean to get in the middle of the
family drama but if you guys are cooking
hot dogs how about you all share a
couple with Daddy I'm sure he'd be more
than grateful dr. Robotnik what the hell
are you and your goons doing here
yet just what kind of evil scheme do you
have cooked up for us today oh come on
am I not allowed to just enjoy myself at
the bitch every once in a while I came
to play volleyball with my best friend
Sleet and to collect seashells for my
seashell collection I came because
Robotnik said he would spank me if I
didn't how about you [ __ ] call me
when the hot dogs are done I'll just be
relaxing right here lending my sexy body
soak in the warm sunlight Sleet
get over here and slather my butt cheeks
with some of that sunscreen Dingo go put
sunscreen on Robotnik's ass no pleasure
llamado north of slaughtering Robotnik's
boot with sunscreen
edia velikiy a symbol of pee that no no
foo-foo Yatta Yatta Willy we're a year
that we are rarely family a familiarity
- and so millionaire's the owner throw
well then go right ahead if you insist
big boy I'm all yours Uncle Chuck
nobody's stopping you
Oh
come on don't just let it sit there
you're going to rub it in aren't you and
don't be afraid to really get it in
between the butt crack
don't worry Robotnik yo don't a little
did you meet do you see that's good
cause I wouldn't want anything better
than that damn Charles you're quite the
bad boy aren't you
[Music]
excuse me bartender I would like the
most expensive drink that you've got and
where you're at it I would like another
glass of orange juice for my cue but
here and yes to her you are CEO as Toby
Newport optical bloch pre-social you
twist from two bills while yourself a
view owner that we most certainly earth
we've been having quite the energetic
day so far haven't we be mark levy I
just wanted to say that I'm sorry I'm so
sorry for being a big baby around water
I'm so sorry for disappointing you today
I know you had high expectations and I
let you down you even wasted all that
money on that speedo which is useless
now I hope you don't hate me go [ __ ] I
could never hate you
all I've ever wanted is the best for you
someday you'll learn to swim I know you
will you just have to keep believing in
yourself I'm sorry he did not love area
with the USA tail don't never to swim
that's right my boyfriend Bart Lobby has
been trying to teach me all morning
No until my high grow he was just
looking he couldn't swim al and this
bunny what they are mad machine evil but
you're working at bitch so you must know
how to swim
how would you overcome your fears yep
and free destroyed Oh tell busy William
fab limo he will tell you and they owe
me family came to the bitch me fatty was
so exited to teach my auto swim so
exiting in fact they arrived at a killer
swimming defi from Shaw he won was well
he died champagne and swimmers the water
also equity tests Eva to get under the
geranium beautiful GU Qing commute off
today internet Oh
if I have a picture of today if you want
to see a time
well is that you you look so scared
II Neiman took the photo figure he'll
consummate Colleen for me damn a veil
she stood have fun he need a cannon for
him he can blow [ __ ] well and just
seeing your dad and travel made you get
over your fears of water daddy he guess
you could say that so together losing my
daddy more even skeletons are who I tell
itself your daddy's a hotel Dino ever
well well well so this is where my
[ __ ] were I've been looking for you
all [ __ ] morning
Knuckles my man how's it hanging I
didn't expect to see you here at the
bitch today it's going good
you know me I'm just here to build
sandcastles and pick up [ __ ] ha ha ha
speaking of [ __ ] there's a little
rumor going around town that you're
finally learning how to swim and you
know what big guy I couldn't be more
proud of you it's about damn time Sonic
the Hedgehog stopped being a little
[ __ ] well so people are already talking
about it around town huh you bet your
big blue as they are when were knocked
out that the famous Sonic the Hedgehog
was finally going to learn how to swim
it's over could talk about there's not a
single newspaper in town square that
doesn't have your face on the there are
even people placing bets about whether
or not you'll succeed of course as your
best bud I would never participate in
such bits I just want you to be happy
[ __ ] is that so then if I may ask why
do you have $300 sticking out of your
butt crack
I don't know how about you mind your own
business and I won't beat your smelly
ass well-read man
well little here why not take a seat and
enjoy a drink with us
bartender please get my britches friend
a glass of your most expensive lemonade
well for real
thanks Bart lobby I definitely will I
didn't even know you knew my name
haha of course I know your name a friend
of my Beach is a friend to me
not man Manic Manic the he God you what
that's not my name
uh-huh I'm only joking with you Sonia
the hit hog
I mean Mandy Uncle Chuck - tad nip
nipples nipples the action
war you have got to be [ __ ] kidding
me is that really the certified swimmers
speedo I heard it goes for about thirty
million dollars and that only seven of
them even exist you bet it is Knox just
one of the many perks of being the
boyfriend of the richest man alive
that's so sick
can I touch it go right ahead it's not
like you're the first person to ask me
that today
war it's so [ __ ] soft it almost feels
like you are not wearing anything yet
because it was made by hand by Egyptian
slaves sewn from the most expensive silk
ever and painted with actual gold dug up
beneath the Egyptian pyramids only the
best from my be
great hit Sonia you really know how to
handle your balls money what they are
Yahoo host standing three four it's
coming right at you shut the [ __ ] up old
man I got this one thanks for driving me
to the bitch today daddy I'm going to go
look for my friends Sonia said she would
be around here somewhere no problem
Mindy just don't have sex with your
boyfriend Manic out in the open again we
don't want to get thrown out of here
like last time holy [ __ ] Mindy are you
okay any money I thought you quit David
well this you're here with him
Mindy Mindy baby I'm so sorry you know I
didn't mean to knock your ass out cold I
guess you could say that I got too
distracted by your big boobies oh is
that so
TV well then I guess I should be on it
yet perhaps you should be [ __ ] what the
hell's going on over here
Oh Sonic Bart levy there you were oh and
hi Knuckles I was wondering when you
were going to show up I uh I really like
your swimsuit it suits you
oh really [ __ ] you know the color scheme
is actually based off of the Jamaican
flag wow that's really cool you bet it
is [ __ ]
I'm going to go get a chili dog before I
throw up
hey bro how is your swimming lesson
going make any progress what do you
think bro I'm a [ __ ] failure I'll
never be able to swim huh well I don't
care that's your a little [ __ ] who
can't swim you'll always be my best bro
how about you come hang out with the
rest of us I bet that will cheer you up
look over there the whole gang just
started playing limbo how low can you go
how low can you go
haha I'll Sh all you [ __ ] how low I
can go
I bet you regret getting that Buju now
don't you [ __ ] I need to go find a
bucket of chili for my hot dog
Wow well if it isn't my lucky day
Sleet come check this out you'll never
believe this [ __ ]
Sleet Slee look look what I found
Sleet Slee look Sleet look Sleet Sleet
Sleet at this it's an orange seashell I
found it's orange like my but doesn't it
look cool
how's it going [ __ ] that's right I'm
talking to you what do you want
shouldn't you be off having sex with
your boyfriend or anything chili dogs
fat boy
that's exactly why I'm here I see your
friend there has chilli in his pocket
give it to me now
you hear him Dingo give Sonic the chili
Noah don't wanna Dingo you don't even
like chili just give it to this fat-ass
but Sleet Robotnik gave it to me as a
Christmas bonus it's precious to me
Dingo Sonic is dating Bart Libby the
richest man on earth
Sonic's not to push over any more now he
can have Bart Levy hire somebody to kick
your ass okay I will give it to him but
I won't like it
I just want to know why the time I come
around gets funny lookin at me up and
down I don't really know you you don't
really know the groove stop back it
makes funny notches you gonna do look at
you who now home on the phone know that
the kid had bought check IDs locally
simmer down you always acting funny to
believe some around you got a new car
but you leasing it now I got a big dog
on the leash I'm releasing them now you
know police in the pound I'm a beast in
the house what the [ __ ] was that
did you just lick your lips that's
[ __ ] creepy that's [ __ ] creepy
Dingo you better go get me a towel
before I shove my fist up your ass
uh-huh you are you cute little bitch
hee-hee Oh Bart levy you found me I
showed it I should have known you were
off looking for food Fat Boy you always
do that come on
what do you say we go hang out with the
others they're roasting marshmallows
marshmallows are disgusting - rich
people such as myself but I know how mad
you live at [ __ ]
so leader Yahoo kids enjoy your diet
average did you ever last wish you raise
hell dad Uncle Chuck in fact I think we
should come back here tomorrow we will
come back here tomorrow only if you end
up doing the chores you promised
hey mama when are my boob is going to be
as big as Mindy Sonia a million things
in your life have to go wrong before
your boobs get as big as hers everybody
look up fireworks are illuminating the
night sky
[Music]
did you have fun at the bitch today
Beach I did Bart levy thanks to you I
promise you
Bart levy someday I will learn to swim
Beach you don't have to promise me
anything
[Music]